<?xml version='1.0' standalone='yes'?>
<log>
<header>
<simName>ASU-RS600</simName>
<componentRole>Host</componentRole>
<project>Seema_Shokoufeh_Track3</project>
<subjectName>Student17Mode2</subjectName>
<timeStamp>2016-12-01_110144</timeStamp>
</header>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: CabFile ../system/devices/default.cab</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: Vehicle Type: Ford Focus</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: "./modules/DatamanTransmit.so" -> Loaded.</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: "./modules/Scenario.so" -> Loaded.</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: "./modules/Vehicle.so" -> Loaded.</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: Registered audio sample ID=0 with sample file=carstart</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: Sim Startup, script: 'vectionStartup.tcl'</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: Core Version: '1.9.39 '</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: Subsystem: "DataMan" Version '1.9.39 ' has registered.</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: Subsystem: "Scenario" Version '1.9.39 A' has registered.</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: Subsystem: "Vehicle" Version '1.9.39 ' has registered.</message>
<message frame='00000000' >DataMan: Priority: 0</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: Priority: 1</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: InitializePlaybackData</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: Record mode, recording to file: ../data/results/Seema_Shokoufeh_Track3/Student17Mode2/Student17Mode2.2016-12-01_110144.playback.bin</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Vehicle: Priority: 3</message>
<message frame='00000000' >DataMan: ------> Starting subsystem: DataMan</message>
<message frame='00000000' >DataMan: Dataman monitoring packet rate at 15 packets per 250475 microseconds</message>
<message frame='00000000' >DataMan: Dataman allowing tolerance of +550 or -550 microseconds</message>
<message frame='00000000' >DataMan: Dataman listening for remote tcp command connections on port 9770</message>
<message frame='00000000' >DataMan: Successfully prequeued next connection</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: ------> Starting subsystem: Scenario</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: starting scenario</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: starting subject</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: The MainHudChannel is 1</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: No options have been enabled.  0</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: loading road network ../data/projects/Seema_Shokoufeh_Track3/Seema_Shokoufeh_Track3.net</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: Scenario found 0 intersections</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: Scenario found 0 feature sets</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: regions from network are 10158</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: loading polygon file ../data/projects/Seema_Shokoufeh_Track3/Seema_Shokoufeh_Track3.terrain</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: total regions are 15095</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: File:  ../data/projects/Seema_Shokoufeh_Track3/Seema_Shokoufeh_Track3.quad does not exist</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: Building quad tree</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: quad tree takes 15415204 bytes</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: Done building quad tree and saving to file</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: we are using a page size of 300.000000</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: pages created</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: ambientDensity = 1.000000</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: broadcast locations for 0 semaphores</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: Done initializing scenario.  Maximum number of vehicles is 512</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: There are 1 collidable static entities</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: There are 28 tile instances</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: EntityCreate: CAR4 of type Caprice Red at pos 403.40, 91.90, -0.00, heading -90, vel 0.00 MPH.  It can not be automatically destroyed</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: EntityCreate: CAR1 of type Caprice Red at pos 1904.00, 423.00, -0.00, heading 0, vel 0.00 MPH.  It can not be automatically destroyed</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: TriggerCreate: Creating Trigger TriggerC1 at 1904, 423</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: EntityCreate: CAR3 of type Caprice Red at pos 92.20, 1596.30, -0.00, heading 179, vel 0.00 MPH.  It can not be automatically destroyed</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: TriggerCreate: Creating Trigger TriggerSTOP1 at 1907.8, 1603.3</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: TriggerCreate: Creating Trigger TriggerC2 at 1907.7, 1627.1</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: EntityCreate: CAR2 of type Caprice Red at pos 1595.70, 1907.40, -0.00, heading 90, vel 0.00 MPH.  It can not be automatically destroyed</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: SimSelectDataCollectionElements: Data Collection elements have been set</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: SimCreateDataCollectionElement: Element named GrabData</message>
<error frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: SimCollectData: Entity to monitor (Vehicle96) was not found.  Monitor entity is currently NONE.</error>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: SimCollectData: Data Collection On, Rate 60, Entity NONE, ZoneName Unknown</message>
<error frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: SimSetMonitorEntity: Entity to monitor (Vehicle96) was not found.  Monitor entity is currently NONE.</error>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: SimSetUserData: User data GrabData set to Terminate</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: VTriggerCreate: Created vtrigger 0: Speedmtr</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: SCM: VTriggerAdd: Added vtrigger 'Speedmtr'</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: Leaving ScriptReadFile</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Scenario: ScriptSystem: Initialization Complete.</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Vehicle: ------> Starting subsystem: Vehicle</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Vehicle: Starting RTAI</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Vehicle: Io Memory created</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Vehicle: Vehicle Io Memory set.</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Vehicle: Successfully initialized the Vehicle interface</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Vehicle: Dyn Start Commmand ./Dynamics c=t m=t d=../data/dynamics/Small b=../system/devices/default.cab</message>
<message frame='00000000' >Vehicle: Waiting to receive sncSemaphore</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: RT: 0 is DataMan</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: RT: 1 is Scenario</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: RT: 2 is Vehicle</message>
<message frame='00000000' >SimCore: mlockall(MCL_CURRENT) returns: 0</message>
<warning frame='00000001' >Vehicle: Frame Overrun -Possibly scenario taking too long! Semephore value is: 1</warning>
<message frame='00000002' >Scenario: SCM: Trigger: 'TriggerC1' activated by Subject</message>
<message frame='00000002' >Scenario: SCM: EntityJoinRoadway: CAR1: Command Added: </message>
<message frame='00000003' >Scenario: SCM: EntitySetAcceleration: CAR1 has new accel rates: norm 6.000000, max 6.000000 m/ss</message>
<message frame='00000003' >Scenario: SCM: EntitySetRoadwayVelocity: CAR1: using fixed speed 26.822000 m/s</message>
<message frame='00000003' >Scenario: SCM: EntityJoinRoadway: CAR1 attached to roadway!</message>
<message frame='00000015' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 601747 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 40000 usecs</message>
<message frame='00000030' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 264876 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 40000 usecs</message>
<message frame='00000045' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 241000 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 40000 usecs</message>
<message frame='00000060' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252714 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 20000 usecs</message>
<message frame='00000060' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 135 in color 0, 255, 0 text '0'</message>
<message frame='00000075' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 246769 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 10000 usecs</message>
<message frame='00000105' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 249692 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 5000 usecs</message>
<message frame='00000120' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252675 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 5000 usecs</message>
<message frame='00000120' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 137 in color 0, 255, 0 text '0'</message>
<message frame='00000135' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 251208 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 2500 usecs</message>
<message frame='00000150' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 249535 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 2500 usecs</message>
<message frame='00000180' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 138 in color 0, 255, 0 text '0'</message>
<message frame='00000240' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 139 in color 0, 255, 0 text '0'</message>
<message frame='00000300' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 140 in color 0, 255, 0 text '0'</message>
<message frame='00000360' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 142 in color 0, 255, 0 text '0'</message>
<message frame='00000420' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 144 in color 0, 255, 0 text '3'</message>
<message frame='00000480' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 145 in color 0, 255, 0 text '8'</message>
<message frame='00000540' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 148 in color 0, 255, 0 text '13'</message>
<message frame='00000600' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 149 in color 0, 255, 0 text '18'</message>
<message frame='00000660' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 151 in color 0, 255, 0 text '23'</message>
<message frame='00000720' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 152 in color 0, 255, 0 text '26'</message>
<message frame='00000780' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 154 in color 0, 255, 0 text '29'</message>
<message frame='00000840' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 156 in color 0, 255, 0 text '31'</message>
<message frame='00000900' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 157 in color 0, 255, 0 text '34'</message>
<message frame='00000960' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 159 in color 0, 255, 0 text '36'</message>
<message frame='00001020' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 160 in color 0, 255, 0 text '38'</message>
<message frame='00001080' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 162 in color 0, 255, 0 text '39'</message>
<message frame='00001140' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 163 in color 0, 255, 0 text '40'</message>
<message frame='00001200' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 165 in color 0, 255, 0 text '41'</message>
<message frame='00001260' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 167 in color 0, 255, 0 text '42'</message>
<message frame='00001320' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 170 in color 0, 255, 0 text '43'</message>
<message frame='00001380' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 171 in color 0, 255, 0 text '43'</message>
<message frame='00001440' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 172 in color 0, 255, 0 text '44'</message>
<message frame='00001500' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 174 in color 0, 255, 0 text '44'</message>
<message frame='00001560' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 175 in color 0, 255, 0 text '44'</message>
<message frame='00001620' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 177 in color 0, 255, 0 text '45'</message>
<message frame='00001680' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 179 in color 0, 255, 0 text '45'</message>
<message frame='00001740' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 181 in color 0, 255, 0 text '46'</message>
<message frame='00001800' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 183 in color 0, 255, 0 text '46'</message>
<message frame='00001860' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 184 in color 0, 255, 0 text '47'</message>
<message frame='00001920' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 186 in color 0, 255, 0 text '47'</message>
<message frame='00001980' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 188 in color 0, 255, 0 text '48'</message>
<message frame='00002040' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 189 in color 0, 255, 0 text '48'</message>
<message frame='00002100' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 191 in color 0, 255, 0 text '48'</message>
<message frame='00002160' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 193 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00002220' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 196 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00002280' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 198 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00002340' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 199 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00002400' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 200 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00002460' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 202 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00002520' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 203 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00002580' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 205 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00002640' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 206 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00002700' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 207 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00002760' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 209 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00002773' >Scenario: SCM: Trigger: 'TriggerSTOP1' activated by CAR1</message>
<error frame='00002773' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetAcceleration: Unable to find entity "Vehicle3"</error>
<error frame='00002773' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetRoadwayVelocity: Entity Vehicle3 not found</error>
<message frame='00002820' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 211 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00002880' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 212 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00002940' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 214 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00003000' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 217 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00003060' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 218 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003120' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 220 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003180' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 221 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003240' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 223 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003300' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 225 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003360' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 226 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003420' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 227 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003480' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 229 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003540' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 231 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003600' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 233 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003660' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 234 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003720' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 237 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003780' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 240 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003840' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 241 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00003900' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 243 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00003960' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 244 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00004018' >Scenario: SCM: Trigger: 'TriggerC2' activated by Subject</message>
<message frame='00004018' >Scenario: SCM: EntityJoinRoadway: CAR2: Command Added: </message>
<message frame='00004019' >Scenario: SCM: EntitySetAcceleration: CAR2 has new accel rates: norm 6.000000, max 6.000000 m/ss</message>
<message frame='00004019' >Scenario: SCM: EntitySetRoadwayVelocity: CAR2: using fixed speed 26.822000 m/s</message>
<message frame='00004019' >Scenario: SCM: EntityJoinRoadway: CAR2 attached to roadway!</message>
<message frame='00004020' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 245 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00004080' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 246 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00004140' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 249 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00004200' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 250 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00004260' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 252 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00004320' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 254 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00004380' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 255 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00004440' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 256 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00004495' >Scenario: SCM: Trigger: 'TriggerSTOP1' activated by Ambient168</message>
<error frame='00004495' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetAcceleration: Unable to find entity "Vehicle3"</error>
<error frame='00004495' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetRoadwayVelocity: Entity Vehicle3 not found</error>
<message frame='00004500' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 257 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00004560' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 262 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00004620' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 263 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00004680' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 264 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00004740' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 265 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00004800' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 269 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00004860' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 270 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00004886' >Scenario: SCM: Trigger: 'TriggerSTOP1' activated by Ambient261</message>
<error frame='00004886' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetAcceleration: Unable to find entity "Vehicle3"</error>
<error frame='00004886' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetRoadwayVelocity: Entity Vehicle3 not found</error>
<message frame='00004920' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 272 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00004980' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 273 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005040' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 275 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005094' >Scenario: SCM: Trigger: 'TriggerSTOP1' activated by Ambient266</message>
<error frame='00005094' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetAcceleration: Unable to find entity "Vehicle3"</error>
<error frame='00005094' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetRoadwayVelocity: Entity Vehicle3 not found</error>
<message frame='00005100' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 276 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005160' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 278 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005220' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 279 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005280' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 281 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005300' >Scenario: SCM: Trigger: 'TriggerSTOP1' activated by Ambient267</message>
<error frame='00005300' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetAcceleration: Unable to find entity "Vehicle3"</error>
<error frame='00005300' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetRoadwayVelocity: Entity Vehicle3 not found</error>
<message frame='00005340' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 282 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005341' >Scenario: SCM: Trigger: 'TriggerSTOP1' activated by Ambient274</message>
<error frame='00005341' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetAcceleration: Unable to find entity "Vehicle3"</error>
<error frame='00005341' >Scenario: SCM: ERROR: EntitySetRoadwayVelocity: Entity Vehicle3 not found</error>
<message frame='00005400' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 284 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005460' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 285 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005520' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 287 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005580' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 289 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005640' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 292 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005700' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 293 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005760' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 294 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005820' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 296 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005880' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 297 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00005940' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 299 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006000' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 300 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006060' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 301 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006120' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 303 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006180' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 305 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006240' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 306 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006300' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 309 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006360' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 310 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006420' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 312 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006480' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 314 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006540' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 315 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006600' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 317 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006660' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 318 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006720' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 320 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006780' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 321 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006840' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 323 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006900' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 325 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00006960' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 326 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00007020' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 327 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00007080' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 328 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00007140' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 330 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00007200' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 332 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00007245' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 253474 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 1250 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007260' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 255990 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007260' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 335 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00007275' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 255847 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007290' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 255452 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007305' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 254952 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007320' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 254513 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007320' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 336 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00007335' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 254016 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007350' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 253975 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007365' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 253604 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007380' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252678 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007380' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 337 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00007395' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252618 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007410' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252409 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007425' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252134 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007440' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 251400 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007440' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 339 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00007455' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 251057 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00007500' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 340 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00007560' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 342 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00007620' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 343 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00007680' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 345 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00007740' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 347 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00007800' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 348 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00007860' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 349 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00007920' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 350 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00007980' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 351 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008040' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 356 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008100' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 357 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008160' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 358 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008220' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 360 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008280' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 362 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008340' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 363 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008400' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 365 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008460' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 366 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008520' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 367 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008565' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 246120 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 625 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008580' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 245764 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008580' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 369 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008595' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 245774 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008610' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 245757 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008625' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 245762 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008640' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 245865 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008640' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 370 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008655' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 245979 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008670' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 246077 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008685' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 246249 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008700' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 246508 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008700' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 372 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008715' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 246823 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008730' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 247093 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008745' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 247214 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008760' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 247339 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008760' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 373 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00008775' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 247568 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008790' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 247814 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008805' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 248038 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008820' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 248266 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008820' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 376 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00008835' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 248456 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008850' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 248642 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008865' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 248808 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008880' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 248976 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008880' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 377 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00008895' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 249195 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008910' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 249394 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008925' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 249604 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008940' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 249773 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00008940' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 378 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009000' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 379 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009060' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 380 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009120' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 381 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009180' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 384 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009195' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 249845 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00009240' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 385 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009300' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 386 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009360' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 389 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009420' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 390 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009480' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 391 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009540' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 393 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009600' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 394 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009660' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 396 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009690' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 249911 microseconds, telling realtime to speed by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00009720' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 397 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009780' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 398 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009840' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 400 in color 0, 255, 0 text '52'</message>
<message frame='00009900' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 402 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00009960' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 403 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00010020' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 404 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00010080' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 405 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00010140' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 409 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00010200' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 410 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00010260' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 411 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00010320' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 412 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00010380' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 413 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00010440' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 414 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00010500' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 417 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00010560' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 418 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00010620' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 420 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00010680' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 421 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00010740' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 423 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00010800' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 425 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00010860' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 426 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00010920' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 430 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00010980' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 431 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00011040' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 432 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00011100' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 433 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00011160' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 435 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00011220' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 437 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00011280' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 438 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00011340' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 439 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00011400' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 442 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00011460' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 443 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00011520' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 444 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00011580' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 445 in color 0, 255, 0 text '49'</message>
<message frame='00011640' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 446 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00011700' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 448 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00011715' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 253757 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011730' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 255719 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011745' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 255474 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011760' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 255415 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011760' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 452 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00011775' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 255401 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011790' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 255259 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011805' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 254972 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011820' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 254707 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011820' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 453 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00011835' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 254567 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011850' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 254312 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011865' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 253957 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011880' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 253828 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011880' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 454 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00011895' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 253797 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011910' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 253661 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011925' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 253486 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011940' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 253379 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011940' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 456 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00011955' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 253106 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011970' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252869 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00011985' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252592 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00012000' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252406 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00012000' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 457 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00012015' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252138 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00012030' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252162 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00012045' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 252044 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00012060' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 251869 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00012060' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 459 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00012075' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 251731 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00012090' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 251421 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00012105' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 251246 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00012120' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 461 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00012180' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 462 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00012240' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 463 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00012300' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 466 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00012360' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 467 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00012420' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 470 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00012480' >DataMan: Dataman packet delivery delta is: 251027 microseconds, telling realtime to slow by 312 usecs</message>
<message frame='00012480' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 471 in color 0, 255, 0 text '50'</message>
<message frame='00012540' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 474 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00012600' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 475 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00012660' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 476 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00012720' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 478 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00012780' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 479 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00012840' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 482 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00012900' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 483 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00012960' >Scenario: SCM: VisualsDisplayText: Displaying text speed textID 486 in color 0, 255, 0 text '51'</message>
<message frame='00012964' >Vehicle: Kill/Keyboard SIGTERM caught!</message>
<warning frame='00012964' >Vehicle: Frame Overrun -Possibly scenario taking too long! Semephore value is: 65533</warning>
<message frame='00012964' >SimCore: Starting to shutdown simulation</message>
<message frame='00012964' >DataMan: Preparing to shutdown: DataMan</message>
<message frame='00012964' >DataMan: Subsystem DataMan passed Startup()</message>
<message frame='00012964' >DataMan: DataMan Being Shutdown</message>
<message frame='00012964' >Scenario: Preparing to shutdown: Scenario</message>
<message frame='00012964' >Scenario: Subsystem Scenario passed Startup()</message>
<message frame='00012964' >Scenario: Scenario Being Shutdown</message>
<message frame='00012964' >Vehicle: Preparing to shutdown: Vehicle</message>
<message frame='00012964' >Vehicle: Subsystem Vehicle passed Startup()</message>
<message frame='00012964' >Vehicle: Vehicle Being Shutdown</message>
<message frame='00012964' >SimCore: Shutting down tcl system</message>
<message frame='00012964' >SimCore: Shutting down simulation</message>
<results>
  <shutdown source = 'external' success = 'true'/>
</results>
<report></report>
</log>
